[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
‎DOCTOR X: MAFIA IN WHITE
‎Stay here.
‎I'll get your brother out.
‎EPISODE 2
‎The surgery press release goes out today.
‎Director Bu.
‎We were able to expand ‎the pediatric cancer ward
‎thanks to this gentleman's donation.
‎As the only branch running at a deficit--
‎He's definitely a patient.
‎In more ways than one.
‎The foundation's hospitals ‎net tens of billions of won.
‎Do we still need to cater to VIP donors?
‎The surgical staff room expansion ‎is on hold right now,
‎and the foundation ‎won't give us an answer.
‎Please put together ‎the past donation records.
‎We should be doing upfront chemo.
‎Why are we doing surgery first, Dr. Do?
‎The patient insists on it.
‎I can't persuade him.
‎He says he needs to stay sharp right now.
‎You can't blame him ‎if you take a look outside…
‎WAGE WITHHOLDING, MISMANAGEMENT, ‎AND ABUSE OF POWER
‎He just arrived.
‎Dr. Ma Seong-gyu is downstairs.
‎Dr. Do.
‎Can you do it?
‎MONTHLY RENTALS AVAILABLE
‎1.5 MILLION PER MONTH (NEGOTIABLE)
‎It's 1.5 million won a month?
‎So freaking expensive.
‎GUSEO UNIVERSITY SEONAM MEDICAL CENTER
‎Park Gwang-cheol, step down!
‎-Step down! ‎-Step down!
‎Stop withholding wages!
‎-Stop withholding! ‎-Stop withholding!
‎Park Gwang-cheol, get out!
‎-Get out! ‎-Get out!
‎Stop withholding wages!
‎-Stop withholding! ‎-Stop withholding!
‎Are you here for yourself, ‎or is someone else sick?
‎-No, thank you. ‎-Just take it.
‎Think of me as your grandma and eat it.
‎I can eat that without a problem.
‎Thank you.
‎Stop withholding wages!
‎-Stop withholding! ‎-There he is!
‎We're patients too.
‎Look, he's going inside.
‎-We're all patients here. ‎-All of us are here to see a doctor.
‎We're patients too!
‎Let me ask you something.
‎Yes, sir.
‎I'm really sick, aren't I?
‎I actually have cancer?
‎Yes, you have cancer.
‎No one believes me.
‎I've faked being sick ‎to dodge the parliamentary audit.
‎And I faked collapsing ‎to postpone my trial.
‎Now that I'm actually sick…
‎I can barely stand, ‎but they're kicking up a fuss.
‎Getting stressed ‎will make your condition worse.
‎Dr. Do has in-depth knowledge ‎of treatment and management
‎on top of excellent surgical skills.
‎You're in good hands.
‎You'll go far.
‎Thank you. I'm Ma Seong-gyu, by the way.
‎Before we go up to my room,
‎let's stop by ‎the pediatric cancer ward I funded.
‎I couldn't bask in the glory of it ‎because of the trial.
‎I hear there's a plaque ‎with my name on it.
‎Yes, sir.
‎This is the story of a lone wolf.
‎Hey, Gye Su-jeong.
‎I need this.
‎A solitary figure that has emerged ‎in the era of mafia in white,
‎where even the practice of saving lives ‎is driven by money and power.
‎Emergency patient!
‎She belongs to no group.
‎She belongs to no system.
‎Dr. Gye!
‎This person right here…
‎Why that…
‎-Gye Su-jeong! ‎-…despises authority
‎-and answers to no one. ‎-Wait!
‎Her only weapons are her medical license
‎and the surgical skills ‎she has honed from the bottom up.
‎No pneumothorax.
‎Miss, what's your name?
‎Lee Ju-hui.
‎I have type 1 diabetes.
‎-Pull up her EMR now. ‎-Yes, Doctor.
‎This is humiliating.
‎Who was that crazy lady?
‎Meet Gye Su-jeong, a surgeon.
‎Also known as‎…
‎Doctor X.
‎Sun and Steel's chairman, ‎Park Gwang-cheol,
‎has allegedly faked being a patient…
‎Man, seriously?
‎…‎in order to suspend ‎the execution of his sentence.
‎Are we really working with her?
‎We have to.
‎Director Bu decided on it,
‎and we're short on staff.
‎But come on, she does whatever she wants.
‎She had an emergency patient.
‎Well, yes.
‎But my face is plastered ‎all over the news now.
‎Hey, you look great on camera.
‎Oh, come on.
‎Hang in there.
‎Let's get revenge.
‎Let's throw her off so she can't focus.
‎Okay.
‎-Do you want coffee? ‎-Yes, coffee.
‎Yeah, coffee.
‎Earbuds.
‎I need you to assist with ‎Dr. Do's surgery.
‎You're not going in?
‎It'd be too obvious if I went in.
‎He'll definitely know ‎that I don't trust his surgical skills
‎if I try to assist.
‎But you're at the right level ‎to assist him.
‎Sure.
‎Anyway, how did Dr. Do end up…
‎It happened over drinks.
‎I guess Dr. Do was attentive to him,
‎which put the chairman in a great mood.
‎So he assigned Dr. Do ‎as his primary attending.
‎He chose his primary attending ‎based on his mood?
‎He knew that everyone here ‎would fight over his surgery,
‎so he just chose the easiest one ‎to push around.
‎And Dr. Do couldn't refuse.
‎Piece of trash.
‎"Piece of trash"?
‎Don't make eye contact.
‎Right.
‎-Don't look at her. ‎-Don't look.
‎Feels like she won.
‎The surgical staff room ‎used to feel like home,
‎but now it's too uncomfortable.
‎Let's use the partition here to hide her.
‎-Want to put it up? ‎-Yes.
‎Yeah, good idea.
‎-Not seeing her makes me anxious. ‎-I can't tell what she's doing.
‎-Should we put it away? ‎-Should we?
‎-Put it away. ‎-Yes.
‎Lift it.
‎Put it away.
‎-Seeing her makes me uncomfortable. ‎-Darn it.
‎I'm uncomfortable when I see her, ‎anxious when I don't.
‎She gets on my nerves.
‎-Hello, Dr. Do. ‎-Hello.
‎Put that over there.
‎What?
‎I mean, yes, sir.
‎You came to work, Dr. Gye.
‎No, people walk through here.
‎I didn't tell you to put it there. ‎Move it up.
‎What?
‎Put it on the desk.
‎But Dr. Gye's desk is…
‎Let's do this, intern.
‎What's this?
‎My employment terms.
‎"Joining director rounds, ‎attending rounds, and work dinners."
‎I don't do that.
‎"Writing papers for attendings ‎and compiling data."
‎I don't do those either.
‎I know.
‎I didn't bring the files here ‎for you to prep my paper.
‎I just pulled whatever might be useful.
‎You can take a look if you want.
‎But…
‎I'm afraid ‎there's nowhere else to put them.
‎This room is just so small.
‎I'll take some and put them on my desk.
‎-It'll be easier for Dr. Gye… ‎-Hey, Park Tae-gyeong.
‎-Hey, Dr. Park. ‎-Dr. Gye?
‎Does she even have anywhere else to go?
‎-Nice. ‎-Dr. Park.
‎So, how's life as an intern these days…
‎From now on, you're Gye Su-jeong's CCTV.
‎What?
‎Keep an eye on Dr. Gye.
‎But I'm an intern, sir.
‎I have to study.
‎I assisted multiple attendings ‎while doing my studies.
‎You just need to watch one mad dog.
‎-"Mad dog"? ‎-Yeah.
‎After that last surgery, ‎we're calling her a mad dog.
‎Not "mad doc." It's "mad dog."
‎That's what we decided.
‎That seems pretty harsh.
‎It's not nice to call people names.
‎How would you feel ‎if people called you "Ma Fork-gyu"?
‎What did you just say?
‎Oh, the CCTV power is on now.
‎"Fork-you"?
‎Goodness.
‎I've been looking all over for you.
‎Are you going to work from here? ‎Then let's go in.
‎Oh, you left your bag in the staff room.
‎I have my wallet. It's my treat…
‎Strawberry cake, ‎Earl Grey pound cake, a croffle combo,
‎and one large, sweet vanilla latte.
‎Bring her here.
‎Bring that mad dog right now.
‎It seems it was such an emergency
‎that she wasn't thinking.
‎Hey.
‎Mr. New-Director, listen up.
‎If I die, a lot of people will--
‎Will be so sad and upset, of course.
‎They'll have it easy.
‎They'll be very happy ‎to blame me for everything.
‎They'll dump the mess they made ‎right into my grave.
‎Which is why
‎you need to save my life.
‎Do whatever it takes to save me, got it?
‎Answer me!
‎-Yes, sir. ‎-Yes, sir.
‎It's nice to see you enjoy your food.
‎Oh, you probably need your bag…
‎You had your wallet? Then why didn't you…
‎I'm broke.
‎Why are you broke?
‎"Employment terms. ‎No personal talk whatsoever."
‎What if I get you some blueberry cake--
‎I spent my allowance.
‎You get an allowance? From whom?
‎-Ms. Jang at the agency. ‎-I see.
‎So she manages your money.
‎Do you live together?
‎But your salary isn't peanuts ‎like some kid's allowance.
‎How much do you get?
‎A hundred thousand won.
‎A hundred thousand won per day is plenty.
‎-Per month. ‎-What?
‎That's insane. ‎Does she have something on you?
‎I'm in debt.
‎What? Is it a lot?
‎Yeah. I get in trouble if I don't listen.
‎Trouble?
‎What do you mean? ‎Does she hit you or something?
‎Yeah. She hits me.
‎She hit me yesterday ‎because I spent my allowance.
‎By any chance,
‎did this Ms. Jang ‎take your passport or ID?
‎Yeah. She takes care of all that.
‎Su-jeong likes cake
‎Su-jeong, here's some tasty cake.
‎Cake!
‎If you want it, go to work and make money.
‎You doctor-slave.
‎Put your hands up!
‎I need your signature.
‎I took out a loan under your name.
‎I want more of this.
‎Of course.
‎I can buy however much you want.
‎I have a lot of money.
‎Eat as much as you want.
‎You're a good person.
‎Until I finish this, that is.
‎Do you crave anything these days?
‎-Jjajangmyeon. ‎-I'll treat you someday.
‎Treat me today.
‎When do you get off? I leave at six.
‎But I don't. Come on, you know that.
‎Get off work with me.
‎I'm sure kiosks aren't easy
‎for patients or elderly people, ‎even with a kiosk attendant.
‎I'm still young, but you saw ‎how much trouble I had too.
‎It's hard to read, you get nervous…
‎And you worry about the people behind you.
‎-Right. Then you freeze up even more. ‎-Excuse me.
‎And it makes you think you're incompetent.
‎May I help you?
‎Yes, please.
‎Thank you.
‎Still, it's there to help people.
‎It's there to help the hospital.
‎Does that look like it helps people?
‎I didn't think ‎you'd notice things like that.
‎Try not to think too much ‎about what happened in the staff room.
‎What?
‎Getting kicked out…
‎You know, getting bullied.
‎I had no idea.
‎Anyway, try to ‎keep a low profile for a bit.
‎Yeong-seon.
‎-I would've done this for you. ‎-There you are.
‎I was trying out the kiosk myself.
‎How's Ju-hui?
‎-The pain went away, but now she's mad. ‎-Right.
‎Why is she mad?
‎I can't blame her.
‎She's been sick all her life, ‎and now she has cancer.
‎Of all things…
‎-Insert your credit card. ‎-Your card, please.
‎They want an interim payment.
‎Like we'd skip out on the bill.
‎Hold on.
‎Hey, that over there.
‎What's that vest doing in here?
‎Get rid of that.
‎Get rid of it now.
‎-It's kind of amazing. ‎-You need to leave.
‎-What? ‎-Who are you?
‎-What on earth? ‎-What's going on?
‎What are you doing?
‎-Oh, are you scared? ‎-Yeong-ju, no.
‎Is that why you're doing this?
‎What are you doing?
‎-Give it back! ‎-Wait.
‎She's with me. She's not here to protest.
‎-What are you doing? ‎-Yeong-ju!
‎-Don't push her wheelchair! ‎-Look.
‎-She's with me. ‎-Let go.
‎Take your hands off her! ‎What's wrong with you?
‎-I'm her caregiver. ‎-Hey, it's that nutjob.
‎You said she'd be gone.
‎-Why is she still here? ‎-I'm my sister and niece's caregiver!
‎-Will you please… ‎-Excuse me!
‎Your card's maxed out.
‎My credit card…
‎My wallet is in that vest. ‎Can you give it to my sister?
‎I said let go. Are you insane?
‎-Come on. ‎-What's the matter with you?
‎-Let go of me! ‎-Use your words, okay?
‎-Are you insane? ‎-Just let her go first, okay?
‎Why are you doing this?
‎The less they have, the louder they shout.
‎Look at those pathetic losers.
‎-Sir… ‎-"Pathetic"?
‎Pathetic?
‎And whose fault is this?
‎Give my aunt her paycheck!
‎Give it to her!
‎-Ju-hui! ‎-Pay my aunt right now!
‎Ju-hui!
‎-Ju-hui, stop. ‎-Pay her!
‎-Careful! ‎-Ju-hui!
‎-Has she lost her mind? ‎-What the hell are you doing?
‎Ju-hui!
‎-Come on, guys. ‎-Push!
‎-Stop it! ‎-Ju-hui!
‎-Allow me to push you. ‎-You'll hurt yourself.
‎-Please stop. ‎-Ju-hui, stop!
‎Please let go of her. You'll hurt her.
‎-Please let her go. ‎-Let go of her!
‎Wait a minute!
‎What do you think you're doing?
‎Is that blood?
‎Is she bleeding?
‎-She's bleeding. ‎-Let me take a look.
‎Let go of me now!
‎Ju-hui.
‎-Ju-hui. ‎-Oh god.
‎Are you okay?
‎-Where did the chairman go? ‎-Ju-hui, are you okay?
‎-Where is he? ‎-Ju-hui.
‎-Ju-hui. ‎-You're bleeding.
‎He's right.
‎We're pathetic.
‎Hey.
‎Lee Ju-hui.
‎Lee Ju-hui!
‎Ju-hui.
‎-Ju-hui. ‎-What on earth?
‎What's this blood?
‎You scared me.
‎You're back already? Where's the chairman?
‎I parked him.
‎Hey!
‎Your sister will join ‎after a quick talk with the hospital.
‎Okay.
‎I want you to leave when she comes.
‎Why? I need to be here.
‎Two balls and one strike.
‎Here comes pitch number four.
‎Right down the middle, strike!
‎Two-and-two count.
‎Ma'am, can we step outside
‎and talk about the patient's surgery?
‎Sure.
‎Talk to her when my aunt comes.
‎Just a minute, Doctor.
‎Here.
‎Thank you.
‎Dr. Gye.
‎Type 1 diabetes and a pancreatoblastoma.
‎That's a rare case.
‎Really? Is it that serious?
‎-It's a disaster. ‎-It's a disaster?
‎How did he miss the ball? ‎This inning is a disaster.
‎You're a rare case too.
‎Excuse me.
‎A base hit through the left side!
‎Riding back-to-back hits ‎to build some momentum…
‎Where are you going?
‎Dr. Gye!
‎What is it? What about Dr. Gye?
‎She disappeared.
‎She disappeared? Where to?
‎Yes, Doctor.
‎Oh, Dr. Gye…
‎What? She got into trouble?
‎When did this happen?
‎But she just disappeared.
‎-Dr. Gye… ‎-Where's Dr. Gye? I want to see her face.
‎-I know she's here. ‎-Is that her?
‎There she is.
‎Yeah, that's her. Right?
‎-Yeah. ‎-Look at her enjoying the food.
‎Dr. Gye.
‎-Dr. Gye! ‎-What's going on?
‎What's wrong?
‎Dr. Gye.
‎What were you doing ‎before we went to the café?
‎I was in the hallway.
‎What were you doing there?
‎I saw a dizzy patient lying there,
‎so I asked her a few questions ‎and sent her to ENT.
‎She had Ménière's.
‎What does a temporary worker like you ‎know about Ménière's?
‎Lower your voice, please.
‎You're actually getting upset over that?
‎That patient was waiting ‎for her IM appointment.
‎But now she's lying on a couch in ENT.
‎-Did they run the tests? ‎-We sure did.
‎She can't hear low frequencies, ‎and she has nystagmus.
‎It's Ménière's.
‎Problem solved.
‎That's not the issue!
‎The issue is that she meddled ‎in another department's case.
‎She went from one small-town clinic ‎to another for years
‎where they brushed it off as old age ‎and gave her fluids or strong meds.
‎Her child finally brought her ‎to a big hospital in the city,
‎so why send her in circles?
‎Even her child dismissed her symptoms,
‎saying it was late-life depression.
‎It's true. ‎That's why she held onto me and cried.
‎It's the first time anyone ‎gave her a clear diagnosis.
‎She wept as she thanked me.
‎I was so embarrassed.
‎But wait, did she speak to me informally?
‎-Yes. ‎-Yeah.
‎You're obnoxiously rude, ‎just like the rumors say.
‎How fascinating.
‎How dare a butcher diagnose patients?
‎"How dare a butcher diagnose patients?"
‎-You'd better watch it. ‎-What?
‎How would you feel if a temping internist ‎stole a surgical patient?
‎Let's calm down.
‎This isn't a fight between IM and surgery.
‎The problem is that Dr. Gye here ‎keeps crossing the line,
‎so we should focus on…
‎All right. Just apologize.
‎Oh, I don't need an apology.
‎I just came ‎to put a face to a name.
‎I was curious about ‎the notorious Gye-snake.
‎See you around.
‎You're pretty interesting.
‎See you guys.
‎I need more than an apology.
‎I want to see disciplinary action ‎and a pay cut.
‎None of that applies to me ‎since I'm a temporary worker.
‎How dare you keep…
‎She keeps talking back,
‎but she's not wrong, ‎so you can't argue with her.
‎I get it. Just leave for now.
‎We'll handle things internally
‎and give you an update.
‎You need to set her straight.
‎I won't let this slide.
‎Okay.
‎Jeez, I'm getting heartburn.
‎He's so damn loud.
‎He really does have a nasty temper.
‎He'll be on antacids forever.
‎Why would you do that in the hallway?
‎Pork cutlet.
‎-Can I go back for more? It's good. ‎-What?
‎-Dr. Gye, please read the room. ‎-This place is a hidden gem…
‎-I'll get you some more in a bit. ‎-I…
‎Look…
‎Park Tae-gyeong, where were you?
‎I'm sorry. I had no idea ‎she'd done that in that short time.
‎But I don't think ‎Dr. Gye did anything bad--
‎Right, it wasn't bad.
‎But she did cross the line.
‎On purpose too.
‎What do you mean?
‎To get back to the surgical staff room.
‎She's getting in trouble ‎to get her desk back.
‎Are you saying you kicked her out?
‎You're not kids. ‎What's the matter with you?
‎You're right.
‎Dr. Gye is really meticulous, isn't she?
‎That's what I'm saying.
‎Is that what you really think?
‎Look at her.
‎She's disguising herself
‎by messing up her hair ‎for a few more slices of pork cutlet.
‎You call her meticulous?
‎Our first patient is ‎Park Gwang-cheol, 67 years old.
‎He's a VIP who has supported ‎the hospital over the years.
‎We should make sure ‎he's comfortable during his stay here.
‎The primary surgeon for this case ‎is Dr. Do Yun-sik.
‎That man is a VIP?
‎The diagnosis is pancreatic cancer ‎in the head of the pancreas,
‎measuring 4 cm.
‎We'll proceed with the Whipple procedure.
‎-I'll do my best-- ‎-Objection.
‎There's a possibility the cancer ‎has invaded the SMA or SMV.
‎That won't change anything.
‎The VIP refuses chemotherapy.
‎We'll perform the surgery
‎while preserving the SMA ‎as much as possible.
‎Along with the tumor? ‎Then it's an R2 resection.
‎What's the point of surgery then?
‎He's doing chemo after the surgery.
‎Let's resect it along with the vessel ‎and do an R0 resection.
‎Are you kidding me?
‎An R0 resection?
‎You think we haven't thought of that?
‎Are you trying to get us screwed?
‎Every surgeon knows ‎not to mess with the SMA.
‎Or maybe you don't.
‎I'm okay with messing with it,
‎but I guess you're not.
‎Are you saying you can do it?
‎-Yes. ‎-You'll do it yourself?
‎-If you fail, you'll have to-- ‎-I…
‎don't fail.
‎Our next patient is Lee Ju-hui, ‎a 15-year-old female.
‎She is Dr. Do Yun-sik's patient.
‎Due to the VIP's request ‎to move his surgery up,
‎Ms. Lee Ju-hui's surgery ‎has been rescheduled with her consent.
‎Ms. Lee Ju-hui's surgery…
‎will be performed by Dr. Gye.
‎Director Bu.
‎She's a very important patient ‎for my case report.
‎-I don't approve. ‎-I don't approve either.
‎You think it's acceptable ‎to delay a surgery?
‎Continue.
‎Yes, sir.
‎There's an 8 cm tumor ‎in the body and tail of the pancreas.
‎The imaging scan recommended ‎checking for pancreatoblastoma,
‎so we performed ‎an endoscopic ultrasound-guided biopsy,
‎confirming the diagnosis.
‎Fortunately, there was no evidence ‎of distant metastasis.
‎There.
‎Don't get into trouble, ‎or you'll get fired.
‎Keep to yourself for a bit.
‎You still get to operate.
‎Considering Su-jeong's personality,
‎you think she can do that?
‎Man, that was a narrow escape.
‎If Dr. Do operates,
‎the patient could die.
‎Now that's how you do it.
‎He's that bad?
‎He got his position ‎through papers, research, and politics,
‎not with his surgical skills.
‎That world hospital doctors live in?
‎Face,
‎prestige,
‎and authority.
‎These things hold it together.
‎Without them, they're not doctors.
‎If that's the case, ‎they weren't real doctors to begin with.
‎And when those things…
‎suddenly disappear,
‎that's when we go in.
‎Oh, darn it.
‎-Face down. ‎-Oh, right.
‎This is what you get for losing.
‎How can someone be so blinded by ambition?
‎Ms. Lee Ju-hui is a patient too.
‎Do you get paid more for VIP surgeries?
‎Keep an eye on her tomorrow.
‎And tell her to apologize to IM.
‎See you.
‎-Have a good night, sir. ‎-Thanks.
‎Dr. Gye might come back here tomorrow, so…
‎Complications can include ‎pancreatic fistula, peritonitis,
‎infections, blood clots, ‎pulmonary and cardiac complications,
‎bowel obstruction, ‎and postoperative bleeding.
‎Do you have any questions?
‎Why did the doctor change?
‎I thought he was a senior physician, ‎but she's…
‎She's very good too. I guarantee it.
‎Seriously?
‎He went on about ‎how I was such a rare case
‎and insisted on doing it.
‎What a joke.
‎How long will the surgery take?
‎We estimate around three to four hours.
‎-It's so long. ‎-Yeah.
‎Can I just not do the surgery?
‎What?
‎-What did you just say? ‎-Are you insane?
‎Hey.
‎Your mom and I cashed out ‎your college fund.
‎You need to focus on ‎recovering after the surgery.
‎Let's be real.
‎Even if I live, I won't get into college.
‎So hit the books.
‎I looked it up.
‎The prognosis or whatever ‎wasn't very good.
‎In my condition, ‎I'm pretty much done for, right?
‎Hey.
‎That damn internet ‎is messing with you kids' heads.
‎Don't listen to her.
‎This doctor can do the surgery.
‎Ms. Lee, you need this surgery--
‎How…
‎-How could you say that in front of me? ‎-Stop it, both of you.
‎Let me see the form.
‎We'll sign it now ‎and go outside to bicker.
‎Ms. Lee, please don't do that!
‎-Ju-hui! ‎-Let's stop.
‎-Hey! ‎-I'm sick of this!
‎I've had enough, okay?
‎Look, I'm 15 years old.
‎You know what the kids say?
‎They call me a junkie
‎because I give myself ‎injections in the restroom.
‎You'll die without your insulin shots. ‎They don't know anything.
‎But now I have cancer.
‎Mom, you're in a wheelchair.
‎Isn't it hard to look after me?
‎No. I'm your mother.
‎What about you, Aunt?
‎Let's be honest. ‎It's been the hardest for you.
‎Your sister is in a wheelchair, ‎and your niece has cancer.
‎You take on twice as many ‎wallpapering jobs to support us.
‎And you do the household chores.
‎You don't deserve this.
‎That's for me to deal with.
‎You're making it harder right now. ‎Give me that.
‎Please…
‎Just leave me alone.
‎Just go, all of you.
‎Just let me die!
‎We all die someday.
‎So you don't have to rush things.
‎There's no difference ‎if you die today or next week.
‎-Dr. Gye, you shouldn't say-- ‎-It makes no difference.
‎But without surgery, ‎you'll die within the month.
‎Even if we operate…
‎I guess you'll still die.
‎In about a hundred years.
‎She's 15, so she'd have that long, right?
‎Well…
‎But there's one condition.
‎I operate on you.
‎Because I don't fail.
‎As long as my patient is still breathing, ‎I'll save them no matter what.
‎You decide.
‎Do you want to die in a month, ‎or in a hundred years?
‎"Do you want to die in a month, ‎or in a hundred years?"
‎What was the point of me ‎explaining all that?
‎All it took was that one question.
‎But if you fail, we're in serious trouble.
‎Naturally. Someone could die.
‎Right.
‎Still, you've been reading that chart…
‎What's this?
‎Have you been reading ‎Mr. Park Gwang-cheol's chart?
‎Dr. Gye.
‎I'm counting on you ‎for Ms. Lee Ju-hui's surgery.
‎I could do it, of course,
‎but Director Bu was kind enough ‎to ease my burden.
‎-We got the signed consent form. ‎-Are you sure you don't want to switch?
‎Dr. Gye.
‎At least tell me why you're saying that.
‎You can't do it with your skills.
‎-Hey. Why you… ‎-Sir.
‎Too bad you aren't as good ‎as you are stubborn.
‎We heard that. We can hear you!
‎People can hear you. ‎Please calm down, sir.
‎Seriously?
‎Hold on.
‎Su-jeong, come and eat!
‎-She must be mapping out the surgery. ‎-Yes.
‎She likes operating more than eating.
‎Just one!
‎One for each person.
‎Why won't you go home?
‎You're eating all three meals here.
‎Is today a special day?
‎-You made braised short ribs-- ‎-Hey!
‎Have kimchi.
‎DOCTOR DO YUN-SIK
‎You can't do it with your skills.
‎Ms. Lee Ju-hui's surgery
‎will be performed by Dr. Gye.
‎CASE 2: ABDOMINAL DISCOMFORT ‎DIAGNOSED WITH TYPE 1 DIABETES AT AGE 5
‎Found it.
‎GUSEO UNIVERSITY SEONAM MEDICAL CENTER
‎Right, you have ‎the pancreatoblastoma patient today.
‎In OR 5, right?
‎It's not too late to switch.
‎Let's do a time-out.
‎Stop what you're doing and focus.
‎Patient's name and ID number?
‎It's 11384675,
‎Park Gwang-cheol.
‎OPERATION TIME, TIME, ANESTHESIA TIME
‎Scalpel.
‎The induction was uneventful, ‎and her vitals are good.
‎Then we'll begin with the time-out.
‎Ms. Lee Ju-hui's subtotal…
‎Wipe.
‎Harmonic.
‎Vessel loop.
‎Long Kelly.
‎I see the SMA.
‎Why are you surprised?
‎This is nothing new.
‎This…
‎It shouldn't be like this.
‎What's wrong, Dr. Do?
‎It's spread too much.
‎It's worse than we expected.
‎The vessel…
‎-It's… ‎-It's completely encased by the tumor.
‎It appears the SMA invasion is severe.
‎Yun-sik…
‎What are you going to do?
‎A partial resection
‎won't change the prognosis.
‎We…
‎We'll have to close up.
‎Dr. Do.
‎He's not just any patient. ‎The hospital's fate rides on…
‎Oh, the mic.
‎Dr. Do.
‎Are you really going to close up?
‎What?
‎What if I won't allow it?
‎But Director…
‎Any further resection could do the patient ‎more harm than good.
‎Will you tell the patient you opened, ‎then closed him right back?
‎But…
‎Don't you think
‎you should do everything you can now ‎so you can tell him that later?
‎Then please contact ‎Mr. Park's next of kin…
‎They're not here.
‎No one came. Why would they?
‎Damn it…
‎Everyone's waiting for him to die.
‎His family took turns calling ‎to ask about his chances of survival.
‎This is Bu Seung-gwon.
‎We're not religious.
‎I need to try something.
‎Should I take up a religion?
‎If Ju-hui lives, yes.
‎If she doesn't, no.
‎It'll be their loss.
‎Go grab a bite to eat.
‎I'm fine.
‎Ju-hui went in on an empty stomach.
‎I can hold on too.
‎There's a chocolate bar in the back.
‎Yeong-seon.
‎Look what I found.
‎TO MY FAMILY
‎Transecting the pancreas.
‎Black 60 stapler.
‎This is good.
‎The adhesion isn't too bad.
‎It's still pretty big.
‎I'll get it. Please focus on the surgery.
‎This is OR 5.
‎Right angle.
‎I'm Park Tae-gyeong, an intern. ‎Please go ahead.
‎Not bad.
‎Tell Dr. Gye to come to OR 1.
‎Excuse me?
‎But Dr. Gye is in the middle of surgery.
‎Just have her come.
‎I'm sorry, Director. I can't do that.
‎We need more time here.
‎Dr. Gye needs to operate longer…
‎This is Dr. Gye. I'm on my way.
‎Dr. Gye?
‎Are you giving up on Ms. Lee?
‎-Move. ‎-Why?
‎Because she's not a VIP?
‎Because she's from ‎a low-income, disabled family?
‎Priority.
‎By priority, do you mean success?
‎Is that the kind of doctor you are?
‎I said move.
‎Even when other doctors criticized you ‎for chasing money and success,
‎I never believed it.
‎So how could you do this?
‎You're a doctor!
‎You have a duty to save your patient!
‎You promised her a hundred years!
‎You swore to save her ‎as long as she's breathing.
‎Now it's starting to get fun.
‎You're a doctor!
‎You have a duty to save your patient!
‎You promised her a hundred years!
‎You swore to save her ‎as long as she's breathing.
‎-What are you… ‎-I called her.
‎-Director Bu! ‎-I'm taking over.
‎Sir, you can't do this!
‎Wait a minute. Then…
‎-Who's in charge in OR 5? ‎-Go there if you're worried.
‎Why, you mad dog…
‎Are you insane? ‎Did you abandon the patient?
‎Dr. Bae is already on his way.
‎Out of the way.
‎Move!
‎Dr. Gye.
‎I'm counting on you.
‎As expected. Please move.
‎What will you do?
‎RESECTION PHASE ‎(RESECTION AND VASCULAR DISSECTION)
‎We're going to harvest ‎the great saphenous vein.
‎-What? ‎-Let's open up the drape and prep the leg.
‎Scissors, please.
‎The leg? Why?
‎What do you think you're doing?
‎Why are you changing the procedure? ‎My next surgery is--
‎Please get Dr. Jo from OR 5.
‎What? Hey!
‎Understood.
‎Dr. Kim, please go to OR 5.
‎That won't be necessary.
‎Keep the mean BP at 70.
‎You too, Dr. Jo?
‎How could you leave a patient like this?
‎Try caring about work ethic all the time.
‎-EBL? ‎-It's 100 cc.
‎Prep for vascular anastomosis.
‎Get 7-0 Prolene and the loupes ready.
‎Don't tell me you're trying to get…
‎that ‎vessel.
‎I guess all that research ‎has really sharpened your eye.
‎You.
‎I'd like you to assist me.
‎Get which vessel?
‎I need to know ‎what you're doing to assist.
‎We'll now begin
‎an en bloc Whipple with SMA resection.
‎What?
‎Wait…
‎Are you saying…
‎she finished this in an hour?
‎Yes.
‎Dr. Bae, did the surgery go well?
‎In just an hour?
‎And there's no bleeding.
‎What kind of doctor says that?
‎What?
‎Hemostasis.
‎Yes. Dr. Jo said hemostasis was complete.
‎So this…
‎This is Gye Su-jeong's work?
‎We'll harvest the great saphenous vein ‎from the femoral region,
‎followed by an en bloc resection ‎of the pancreatic cancer,
‎including the SMA and SMV.
‎We'll reconstruct the SMA ‎with the great saphenous vein.
‎For the SMV, we'll use ‎an 8 mm synthetic graft.
‎Hold on!
‎What are you saying?
‎Dr. Do, does she mean…
‎Are you crazy? ‎Are you practicing on a patient?
‎-You're really doing this? ‎-Yes.
‎You can't take such a risk!
‎If you fail, he'll die.
‎He'll die from bowel necrosis!
‎Dr. Do Yun-sik.
‎Follow Dr. Gye's lead.
‎Also, just for the record,
‎Dr. Gye was never in this OR.
‎A self-retaining retractor ‎and loupes, please.
‎Harmonic.
‎EBL is 320 cc.
‎Bowel anastomosis complete.
‎Please monitor the drain output ‎for any signs of bleeding.
‎But you can do that yourself…
‎Wait, are you clocking…
‎This is the least he can do ‎to save face as a senior physician.
‎Director Bu.
‎Double surgeries mean double the fees.
‎I give you my word
‎this will remain confidential ‎from the family and outsiders.
‎-Understood. ‎-However,
‎you'll need to pay in cash.
‎I'll be back soon.
‎I'm sorry, sir.
‎Yun-sik.
‎Your first instinct was to close up.
‎You didn't consider trying anything else.
‎Your first thought was to quit.
‎-But-- ‎-At that moment,
‎you'd already left the OR.
‎I didn't leave!
‎I offered to assist
‎and stayed to the very end…
‎to be useful somehow.
‎Do you know how humiliating that is?
‎Facing that overwhelming wall,
‎knowing my skills ‎aren't good enough to clear it…
‎I…
‎I still…
‎stayed in the OR until the very end.
‎I still held on.
‎And I'll continue to hold on.
‎And…
‎I'll make my mark at this hospital…
‎and achieve everything I've dreamed of.
‎Director Bu.
‎You know, right?
‎You know my dream.
‎All right.
‎I understand.
‎He's so tacky and old-fashioned.
‎And his skills aren't good.
‎But he was pretty cool just now.
‎Yeah.
‎Why are you crouching back here?
‎Oh, have you seen Dr. Gye?
‎That name just ruined the moment.
‎Gye Su-jeong.
‎You went overboard ‎telling him to watch her.
‎Why are you looking for Dr. Gye ‎in the men's locker room?
‎Oh, you're right.
‎-Why? ‎-Well, earlier…
‎It's nothing, sir.
‎Did she really take it out in an hour?
‎Yeah.
‎I think
‎she'd already planned to ‎perform both surgeries.
‎-It's impossible otherwise. ‎-Really?
‎Darn it.
‎I had no idea.
‎Please excuse me.
‎What's wrong with him?
‎TO MY FAMILY
‎To my family.
‎MY AUNT, ME, MY MOM
‎Dear Mom and Aunt‎…
‎Just in case I die today ‎instead of a hundred years from now‎…
‎The two of you
‎love me only because ‎I'm your daughter and niece.
‎Otherwise, I don't think ‎you would've really liked me.
‎But you know what?
‎Even if you weren't my mom
‎or my aunt,
‎I think I would've liked you.
‎Both of you are
‎amazing and wonderful people.
‎That's what I wanted to tell you,
‎instead of things like "I love you."
‎-I'm here. About my shares-- ‎-You're denying it?
‎-It was you, wasn't it? ‎-No, are you serious? It wasn't me.
‎What are you talking about? ‎I suggested the opposite.
‎Oh, come on.
‎Let's get along better
‎next time we meet.
‎But not as each other's caregivers.
‎Let's just have fun together.
‎Promise we'll meet again.
‎-I bought beer. ‎-Great!
‎-Does she know we're having bulgogi? ‎-Yeah.
‎She's probably over there right now.
‎Goodness.
‎She must be so excited.
‎Of course
‎I'm excited too
‎Money's coming in
‎My wallet is smiling
‎I'm so happy
‎LUCKY BATHHOUSE
‎BANANA MILK
‎This is from Chairman Park Gwang-cheol.
‎He wants the surgical team ‎to have dinner on him.
‎All the more reason
‎for me to take it then.
‎CHAIRMAN PARK IN RECOVERY ‎SEARCH AND SEIZURE OF SUN & STEEL
‎That's right.
‎You need to be alive ‎to face punishment and pay the price.
‎Let's see how long you live, Chairman.
‎Look up that procedure right now.
‎-I want details. Hurry up. ‎-Okay.
‎Dr. Gye probably planned to use ‎that procedure before going in, right?
‎That's not important.
‎What matters is its implication.
‎Which is?
‎That she's a mad dog
‎who'll push ahead with surgery ‎no matter the risk to the patient
‎for her own success.
‎Dr. Gye, why are you here ‎and not at your desk?
‎The suck-ups in surgery kicked me out.
‎Oh, the thing is…
‎It's okay. I'm fine here.
‎I already delivered your pay ‎to Ms. Jang for this case.
‎It was a tall order,
‎so I'm grateful.
‎It wasn't much of a tall order.
‎Dr. Gye Su-jeong.
‎I found it.
‎So this is the procedure ‎that Dr. Gye used.
‎There's an article about it ‎from seven years ago.
‎Okay.
‎"The GI surgery team at ‎Cubanacan University of Medical Sciences
‎successfully performed an en bloc Whipple ‎with an SMA reconstruction."
‎"It promised a cure for a patient
‎who had previously been ‎considered inoperable."
‎"However, the patient died
‎two months after the surgery."
‎You're bound to fail at some point.
‎It seems like you've already failed, sir.
‎"The cause of death remains unknown."
‎"The surgeon's name was not revealed."
‎"But the pseudonym in the chart was‎…
‎Doctor X."
‎DOCTOR X: MAFIA IN WHITE
‎Are you saying Dr. Gye is Doctor X?
‎What are you doing?
‎We're losing blood faster ‎than we're losing time.
‎Don't you dare do it every day!
‎The hospital's been ‎in an uproar these days
‎-because of her? ‎-Transfer her now.
‎No. We must treat her here ‎no matter what.
‎We have someone who can operate.
‎I temporarily assigned a new doctor here.
‎-Who is it? ‎-The surgery has begun.
‎Fire her right now.
‎We need to ban her from medicine!
‎Dr. Gye, please wake up!
‎Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim